Guide to the World Student Christian Federation Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- D(f) France, Series XXXIV
  - D(f)500 Organized Lines of Work and Study. Religious Departments and Meetings. General Methods
    - D(f)530 Bible Study
      - D(f)532 Textbooks
        - Items listed in card catalog (Box 142, Folder 1074)
      - D(f)533 Outlines from texts
        - Outlines de la vie de Jesus (Box 142, Folder 1075)
    - D(f)540 Mission study and service. SVM, YMCA. Foreign departments
      - General
        - Couve. Pamphlet re. SVM (Fr.), La FFEC et le probleme missionaire, 1912 (Box 142, Folder 1075)
        - Grauss. Vers l'Unite Chretienne, 1913 (Box 142, Folder 1075)
        - Maury. Les "Volontaires du Christ", n.d. (Box 142, Folder 1075)
      - D(f)542 Textbooks
        - Allier. Le Protestantisme au Japon, 1908 (Box 142, Folder 1075)
      - D(f)544 Mission service. Obligations as to missions implied in Christianity and resting upon the Church
        - Allegret. Etudiants chretiens et Missions, 1906 (Box 142, Folder 1075)
        - Bianquis. Nos Devoirs, 1906 (Box 142, Folder 1075)
      - D(f)549 History of the student missionary movement as distinguished from the SCM as a whole
        - D(f)549.69 Student Discussion Conferences
          - Le Programme des Volontaires du Christ, 1914 (Box 142, Folder 1075)
    - D(f)550 Social study and service. Community welfare work, religious and philanthropic, outside of student body. Home missions
      - General
        - Meuron. La Question sociale et le devoir chretien (Box 143, Folder 1076)
      - D(f)522 Textbooks
        - Lavergne. La valeur sociale, 1914 (Box 143, Folder 1076)
        - Merlin. La Crise du logement, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 1076)
      - D(f)554 Social service. Obligations as to community service implied in Christianity and resting upon the church
        - General
          - Allier. Nos responsabilites, 1913 (Box 143, Folder 1076)
        - D(f)554.1 Enlistment of voluntary service
          - Bosc. L'Appel des Foules, 1913 (Box 143, Folder 1076)
      - D(f)555A Institutions and organizations for social effort on behalf of students
        - Leaflet re. relief for Polish and Austrian students (Box 143, Folder 1076)
        - European Student Relief, n.d. (Box 298, Folder 2739)
        - Bureau de la Mission de Paris, 1940 (Box 298, Folder 2739)
      - D(f)555B Institutions and organizations for social effort by students
        - D(f)555.3 For Armed Forces
          - Pamphlets for persons in war situations (Box 143, Folder 1077)
      - D(f)556 Social morality
        - D(f)556.2 Sex education
          - Bois. Une enquete sur l'Immoralite a l'universite, 1906 (Box 143, Folder 1077)
          - Durrleman. Vers la Purete Personnelle, 1905 (Box 143, Folder 1077)
          - Goy. De la Purete Rationelle, 1907 (Box 143, Folder 1077)
          - Quievreux. La Purete et la Lutte contre l'impurete, 1904 (Box 143, Folder 1077)
  - D(f)600 Associations in Individual Institutions or among Special Classes of Students
    - D(f)610 Colleges, universities and student departments of metropolitan and state associations
      - D(f)611 Objects and field, extension and supervision
        - Pamphlets re. aims/basis of federation (Box 143, Folder 1077)
      - D(f)612 Building and rooms
        - Various appeals for funds, 1907 (Box 143, Folder 1077)
        - Meeting in American church, and appeal for funds, 1907 (Box 143, Folder 1077)
      - D(f)613 Organization, Incorporation
        - D(f)613.1 Constitution and membership
          - Constitution of Etudiants Protestants de Paris, 1897 (Box 143, Folder 1077)
      - D(f)615 Organized lines of work and study. Religious departments and meetings. General methods
        - D(f)615.11 Work with new students
          - Letter to pastors requesting names of persons planning to study in Paris, 1902 (Box 143, Folder 1077)
        - D(f)615.7 Business and publicity. Appeals for financial aid
          - Alger. Creation d'un "Foyer Chretien" (Box 143, Folder 1077)
      - D(f)619 History
        - D(f)619.1 Reports
          - Association des etudiants Protestants de Paris -- Annual reports, 1907-1910 (Box 143, Folder 1077)
        - D(f)619.5 Periodicals
          - Notre Association, 1910 (Box 143, Folder 1077)
    - D(f)620 Professional schools
      - D(f)621 Theological
        - D(f)621.95 Periodicals
          - L'etudiant, 1900-1902 (Box 143, Folder 1078)
    - D(f)650 Schools for Indians
      - D(f)654 Mission service
        - D(f)654.9 History of student missions
          - D(f)654.95 Periodicals
            - Almanach des Missions, 1905 (Box 144, Folder 1079)
    - D(f)660 Associations among special classes
      - D(f)622 Women students
        - General
          - Bidgrain. Les efforts des associations feminines pendant la guerre, 1919 (Box 144, Folder 1079)
        - D(f)622.1 Objects and field
          - Pourquoi des Associations Chretiennes d'Etudiantes?, 1908 (Box 144, Folder 1079)
        - D(f)622.3 Organization, Incorporation
          - Paper re. Objects, 1919 (Box 144, Folder 1079)
          - D(f)622.31 Constitution: l'Association de Paris, 1900? (Box 144, Folder 1079)
    - D(f)690 Foreign
      - Statistics, etc. re. foreign students in France, 1907-1919 (Box 144, Folder 1079)
      - Paper for Chinese students in France, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 1079)
      - Work for Foreign students in France, 1922 (Box 144, Folder 1079)
      - Students' views/experiences, 1925,n.d. (Box 298, Folder 2740)
  - D(f)700 Student Life in General Outside the Federation
    - General
      - Report of student welfare activities in the Latin Quarter of Paris, 1919 (Box 144, Folder 1080)
      - Report on celebrations of the Lausanne Christian Union at Strasbourg, 1919 (Box 144, Folder 1080)
    - D(f)702 University catalogs. Educational bulletins
      - The Schools of France in 1792 and 1914-1917 (Box 144, Folder 1080)
      - Academie de Paris, 1919 (Box 144, Folder 1081)
      - L'Universite de Paris, 1911 (Box 144, Folder 1080)
      - Les Universites et les ecoles francaises, 1914 (Box 144, Folder 1081)
    - D(f)707
      - Discours aux Etudiants, 1900 (Box 145, Folder 1082)
    - D(f)710 Other organizations of students or other classes having interests similar to those of the Federation
      - General
        - Le Cercle Catholique des Etudiants de Paris, 1894 (Box 145, Folder 1082)
        - Le Cercle des Etudiants Protestants de Paris, 1898 (Box 298, Folder 2741)
        - Association Generale des Etudiants de Paris, Annual booklet (Box 145, Folder 1082)
      - D(f)712 Relationships and polity
        - D(f)712.6 International
          - Pour les Unions et pour L'Eglise, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 1082)
    - D(f)720 Buildings and rooms
      - Floor plan of building for Cercle Catholique (Box 145, Folder 1082)
    - D(f)730 Organization, Incorporation
      - D(f)731 Constitutions
        - Cercle Catholique des Etudiants de Paris, 1888 (Box 145, Folder 1082)
        - Paris American Art Association, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 1082)
    - D(f)750 Organized lines of work and study. Religious departments and meetings. General methods.
      - D(f)750.03
        - Leaflet re. Union Chretienne de Jeunes Filles, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 1083)
      - D(f)751 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
        - D(f)751.2 Personal work texts
          - Bois. Le Ministere de la Reconciliation, 1913 (Box 145, Folder 1083)
          - idem. Le Ministere de l'Esprit, 1903 (Box 145, Folder 1083)
          - Monad. Vive l'Alcoolisme!, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 1083)
          - Richard. L'Education de la Volonte, 1904 (Box 145, Folder 1083)
        - D(f)751.8 The individual as citizen. The war. Church and state. Church history
          - A soldier's letter (Box 145, Folder 1083)
      - D(f)752 Devotional and inspirational. The Morning Watch.
        - General
          - Message de Paques, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 1083)
        - D(f)752.2 Days and weeks of prayer
          - D(f)752.23 Song books, religious poetry
            - Cantiques pour soldats, 1915 (Box 145, Folder 1083)
            - Chansons de route de bivouac, 1913 (Box 145, Folder 1083)
      - D(f)753 Bible study
        - General
          - Kaltenbach. L'Etude Personnelle de la Bible, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 1084)
        - D(f)753.2 Textbooks
          - Rayroux. Les Etapes de la Revelation en Israel, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 1084)
          - Vers la Lumiere, 1912 (Box 145, Folder 1084)
          - Le Prophete Amos, 1913 (Box 145, Folder 1084)
      - D(f)755 Social study and service. Community welfare work, religious and philanthropic, outside of student body. Home missions
        - D(f)755.4 Social service. Obligations at to community service implied in Christianity and resting upon the Church
          - Riou. La mission Nationale du Protestantisme, 1912 (Box 145, Folder 1084)
        - D(f)755.5 Institutions and Organizations for Social effort on behalf of students
          - Les Eclaireuses (Box 145, Folder 1084)
        - D(f)755.6 Social morality
          - D(f)755.62 Sex education
            - Bois. La Purete, 1910 (Box 145, Folder 1084)
    - D(f)770 Student Life in general outside the Federation
      - Association Catholique de la jeunesse francaise (ACJF). Reunion des Etudiants, 1917? (Box 146, Folder 1085)
      - Societe de Foyers, Compt Rendu, 1934 (Box 146, Folder 1085)
      - L'Union Chretienne de Jeunes Gens de Langue Francaise de Londres. Le Trait d'union, 1929 (Box 146, Folder 1085)
      - Des Unions Chretiennes de Jeunes Gens de France. L'Esperance, 1935 (Box 146, Folder 1085)
    - D(f)790 History
      - General
        - Les Cinquante Premieres annees des Unions Chretiennes de Jeunes Gens de France, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 1086)
      - D(f)791 Reports
        - General
          - Monet. Francais et Annamites, 1925 (Box 146, Folder 1086)
          - Student Union. 6th Annual Report, 1912 (Box 146, Folder 1086)
          - Paris anglo-american YWCA, 1901-1902, 1908-1909 (Box 146, Folder 1086)
          - British-American YWCA of Paris, 1909-1910, 1911-1912 (Box 146, Folder 1086)
        - D(f)791.2 General Committee Minutes and Documents
          - Les Unions Chretiennes de Jeunes Gens, 1898 (Box 146, Folder 1086)
          - Tokyo conference des Etudiants chretiens, 1908 (Box 146, Folder 1086)
      - D(f)795 Periodicals
        - Foyers-Cantines, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 1087)
        - Almanach de L'Union Nationale des Eglises Reformes Evangeliques, 1915 (Box 146, Folder 1087)
        - Le Muguet, 1912,1914 (Box 146, Folder 1087)
      - D(f)796 Conventions and conferences, educational and legislative
        - D(f)796.1 Plenary conferences
          - Versailles Conference Pour etudiants, 1897 (Box 147, Folder 1088)
        - D(f)796.7 Sundry Conferences
          - Reynolds report at Students' conference in Paris, 1889 (Box 147, Folder 1088)
        - D(f)796.8 Leaders' Conferences
          - Announcement re. Congres International des Etudiants, 1900 (Box 147, Folder 1088)
        - D(f)796.9 Student Discussion Conferences
          - Congres de la Jeunesse Catholique a Besancon, 1898 (Box 147, Folder 1089)
          - National conferences, French YMCA, 1899,1902, 1906 (Box 147, Folder 1089)
          - Corda Fratres Revue Internationale, 1900 (Box 148, Folder 1090)
  - D(f)800 Correspondence
    - D(f)801 John Mott with
      - Prof. Raoul Allier, 1909-22 (Box 148, Folder 1091,92)
      - Edouard de Billy, 1900-19 (Box 148, Folder 1093)
      - Pierre Bouet, 1900-10 (Box 148, Folder 1094)
      - Suzanne de Dietrich, 1926-31 (Box 149, Folder 1095)
      - Charles Grauss, 1906-18 (Box 149, Folder 1096,97)
      - Pierre Maury, 1919-25 (Box 149, Folder 1098,99)
      - Jean Monnier (Box 150, Folder 1100)
    - D(f)810 Ruth Rouse with
      - Raoul Allier, 1911-18 (Box 150, Folder 1101)
      - Suzanne Bidgrain, 1910-19 (Box 150, Folder 1102)
      - Henri Bois, 1916-20 (Box 150, Folder 1103)
      - Suzanne de Dietrich, 1914-22 (Box 150, Folder 1104)
      - Charles Grauss, 1913-14 (Box 150, Folder 1105)
      - Alice Hermann (Madame Jean Gerard), 19171-18 (Box 150, Folder 1106)
      - Lili Kellerman, 1914-16 (Box 150, Folder 1107)
      - Pierre Maury, 1919, 1921-1922 (Box 150, Folder 1108)
      - Lizzie Meyer (Mme. Pierre Maury), 1911-19 (Box 151, Folder 1109)
      - Jeanne Pannier (Mme. Jacques Pannier), 1906-19 (Box 151, Folder 1110)
      - Leo Viguer, 1918-20 (Box 151, Folder 1111)
      - French women students and leaders, 1908-19 (Box 151, Folder 1112)
  - D(f)900 History
    - General
      - Historical documents re. French SCM, 1920-24 (Box 151, Folder 1113)
      - Documents re. Women students work in Federation Francaise des Etudiants Chretiens, 1908-21 (Box 151, Folder 1114)
      - Sundry documents re. Federation Francaise des Etudiants Chretiens, 1908-19 (Box 151, Folder 1115)
      - Documents re. Inter-Confessional question in France, 1908, 1917-1920 (Box 152, Folder 1116)
      - Materials re. Roman Catholic efforts in France, 1909,1922-1923 (Box 152, Folder 1117)
    - D(f)901 Documents on Origins
      - Pamphlet: "Federation Universelle des Associations Chretiennes d'Etudiants", 1920 (Box 298, Folder 2742)
    - D(f)910 Reports
      - General
        - Cercle des Etudiants Protestants de Paris, 1897-98 (Box 152, Folder 1118)
      - D(f)911 Reports of progress. Year books
        - Sous le Ciel Une Seule Famille, 1921-1922 (Box 298, Folder 2743)
      - D(f)911.1 Directories
        - Federation Francaise, 1916/ undated (Box 152, Folder 1118)
      - D(f)912 General Committee Minutes and documents
        - Federation Francaise, 1911-13 (Box 152, Folder 1118)
        - La Conference d'Etudiants, 1908 (Box 152, Folder 1118)
    - D(f)920 Biography in general
      - Alexandre de Faye, 1920 (Box 152, Folder 1119)
      - Roger Allier:, 1890-1914 (Box 152, Folder 1119)
      - Les Cahiers de Jean Kilngebiel: 1892-1917 (Box 152, Folder 1119)
      - Ernest Chavey:, 1894-1917 (Box 152, Folder 1119)
    - D(f)950 Periodicals
      - Bulletin Trimestriel de l'Union Chretienne des Jeunes Gens de Tunis, 1913 Jan (Box 298, Folder 2744)
    - D(f)960 Conventions and conferences, educational and legislative
      - D(f)961Plenary conferences
        - Montpellier, 1903 (Box 152, Folder 1120)
        - Montauben, 1905 (Box 152, Folder 1120)
      - D(f)967 Sundry conferences
        - Conference Chretienne Universelle du Christianisme Pratique, Stockholm, 1925 (Box 152, Folder 1120)
      - D(f)969 Student Discussion Conferences
        - Cercle des Etudiants Protestants du Paris, Pentecote, 1898 (Box 153, Folder 1121)
        - Federation Universelle des Etudiants Chretiens, Zeist, 1905 (Box 152, Folder 1121)
        - Conference pour Etudiants, Montpellier, 1898 (Box 153, Folder 1121)
        - FFEC, Nancy, 1904 (Box 153, Folder 1122)
        - FFEC, Montauban, 1905 (Box 153, Folder 1122)
        - Federation Francaise des Associations Chretiennes d'Etudiants, 1907-1910 (Box 153, Folder 1123)
    - D(f)990 Miscellaneous Historical Documents
      - French comment re. Bale meeting between French and German leaders, 1922 (Box 153, Folder 1124)
- D(h): Portugal, Series XXXV
  - D(h)000 General
    - D(h)030 Service cards and blanks including questionnaires, record and subscription blanks and membership cards
      - Blanks/cards (Box 154, Folder 1125)
  - D(h)100 Objects and field, Extention and supervision
    - Article re. Uma Instituicao Academica Digna De Elogio, in Atlantida (Box 154, Folder 1125)
  - D(h)500 Organized lines of work and study. Religious departments and meetings. General methods
    - D(h)510 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
      - D(h)512 Personal work texts
        - Figueiredo. Factos Notaveis da Historia da Egreja Lusitana, 1909 (Box 154, Folder 1126)
        - idem. Sera Ja O Fim Religiao?, 1911 (Box 154, Folder 1126)
        - Leach. Conhecer-nos-hemos No Ceu, 1909 (Box 154, Folder 1126)
        - Moreira. A Crise nacional e a Solucao protestante, 1910 (Box 154, Folder 1126)
        - Peres. Napoleo Banaparte Nunca Existiu, 1909 (Box 154, Folder 1126)
      - D(h)518 The individual as citizen. The war, church and state. Church history
        - Clark. Os Estudantes na Presente Guerra, 1916 (Box 154, Folder 1127)
    - D(h)520 Devotional and inspirational. The Morning Watch
      - D(h)522 Days and weeks of prayer
        - Unioes Christas da Mocidade, 1904 (Box 154, Folder 1127)
      - D(h)522.3 Song books, religious poetry
        - Humo dos Estudantes Christaos (Box 154, Folder 1127)
    - D(h)550 Social study and service. Community welfare work, religious and philanthropic, outside of student body. Home missions
      - D(h)554 Social service. Obligations as to community service implied in Christianity and resting upon the church
        - Os dois caminhos. Quandros da vida (Box 154, Folder 1127)
    - D(h)560 Entertainment. Athletics. Hygiene
      - Various announcement cards (Box 154, Folder 1127)
    - D(h)570 Business and publicity. Appeals for financial aid
      - Cards with information on YMCA (Box 154, Folder 1127)
  - D(h)600 Associations in individual institutions or among special classes of students
    - D(h)610 Colleges, universities and student departments of metropolitan and state associations
      - General
        - Corres. of Mott w/ Elias Jose dos Santos, 1904 (Box 154, Folder 1128)
      - D(h)611 Objects and field
        - Leaflets re. ACE (Portuguese YMCA) in Coimbra (Box 154, Folder 1128)
    - D(h)630 Secondary schools
      - D(h)631
        - Constitution of ACE, 1920 (Box 154, Folder 1128)
    - D(h)690 Foreign
      - Oporto and its YMCA, 1913 (Box 154, Folder 1129)
  - D(h)700 Student life in general outside the Federation
    - A vida do estudante de Coimbra, 1920 (Box 154, Folder 1129)
    - Postcard of University of Coimbra (Box 154, Folder 1129)
  - D(h)800 Correspondence
    - D(h)810 Ruth Rouse with
      - May Cassells, 1914-1920 (Box 155, Folder 1130)
  - D(h)900 History
    - General
      - Documents re. Portugal, 1914,1922 (Box 155, Folder 1131)
      - Report on YMCA student work in Coimbra, 1922 (Box 155, Folder 1131)
    - D(h)910 Reports
      - Statistics re. Coimbra Students' Christian Association, 1924 (Box 155, Folder 1131)
    - D(h)912 General Committee Minutes and Documents
      - Relatorio, 1905-1909 (Box 155, Folder 1132)
      - Relatorio e Contas, 1907-1908 (Box 155, Folder 1132)
    - D(h)920 Biography in general
      - Article on Mott in O Pequeno Mensageiro, 1903 (Box 155, Folder 1132)
    - D(h)950 Periodicals
      - ACM periodical, 1921 (Box 155, Folder 1133)
      - ACEC Vida Nova, 1922-1923 (Box 155, Folder 1133)
      - Boletin Mensal, 1908-1910 (Box 155, Folder 1134)
      - O Bom Pastor, 1909-1913 (Box 155, Folder 1135)
    - D(h)960 Conventions and conferences, educational and legislative
      - D(h)965 Commissions and Investigations
        - Admission card to Segundo Congresso Nacional das Unioes Christas da Mocidade de Portugal, 1905 (Box 155, Folder 1136)
      - D(h)968 Leaders' Conferences
        - Program for conference in D(h)965, 1905 (Box 155, Folder 1136)
- D(i): Spain, Series XXXVI
  - D(i)700 Student life in general outside the Federation
    - D(i)702 University catalogs. Educational bulletins
      - International Institute for Girls in Spain, annual report, 1915 (Box 156, Folder 1137)
    - D(i)750 Organized line of work and study. Religious departments and meetings. General methods
      - D(i)754 Mission study and service. SVM, YMCA Foreign departments
        - General
          - Evangelisation in Spain. German Mission, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 1137)
        - D(i)754.7 Education, secular and religious, of natives in mission lands
          - Article re. Missionary College, Madrid, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 1137)
        - D(i)754.9 History of the student missionary movement as distinguished from the SCM as a whole
          - D(i)754.95 Periodicals
            - Leaves From Spain, no. 39, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 1137)
  - D(i)800 Correspondence
    - D(i)810 Ruth Rouse with
      - Isabel Alonzo, 1905 (Box 156, Folder 1138)
      - Anna F. Webb, 1905-1906 (Box 156, Folder 1138)
  - D(i)900 History
    - D(i)950 Periodicals
      - Union Cristiana de Jovenes Boletin de Information, 1937 (Box 298, Folder 2745)
    - D(i)960 Conventions and conferences, educational and legislative
      - D(i)961 Plenary Conferences
        - Program for Uniones Cristianas de Jorenes, Barcelona 1926 (Box 156, Folder 1139)
      - D(i)967 Sundry Conferences
        - Letter from Alice Gordon Gulich to Mott, 1897 (Box 156, Folder 1139)
- D(k): Switzerland, Series XXXVII
  - D(k)000 General
    - D(d)011 Publishers' prospectuses, trade lists, announcements
      - Various leaflets, 1910,1913,n.d. (Box 156, Folder 1140)
    - D(k)020 Statistics and charts showing general affiliations and distribution of students
      - CSV, Basel (1882 &1912 compared) (Box 156, Folder 1141)
      - ACE, Lausanne, members recorded, 1910-1912 (Box 156, Folder 1141)
      - ACE, Geneva, 1910-1913 (Box 156, Folder 1141)
      - Graphs for the following cities: Zurich, Bale, Berne, Fribourg, Neushatel, Lausanne, 1901-1912 (Box 156, Folder 1141)
  - D(k)100 Objects and field, Extension and supervision
    - General
      - Notre Association, 1913 (Box 156, Folder 1142)
      - L'Association Chretienne D'Etudiants, 1920 (Box 156, Folder 1142)
    - D(k)120 Relationships and polity
      - D(k)127 To special classes of students
        - D(k)127.7 Other races
          - Jeunesses Orthodoxes, 1930 (Box 156, Folder 1142)
  - D(k)300 Organization, Incorporation
    - D(k)310 Constitution and membership
      - Papers re. and copies of various constitutions (Box 156, Folder 1143)
      - Programs for meetings re. constitutions, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 1143)
      - Proposed changes in the Constitution of the Swiss SCM, 1921 (Box 298, Folder 2746)
    - D(k)330 Membership
      - D(k)332 Basis
        - Buts et methodes d'action des Unions chretiennes de jeunes gens, 1923 (Box 156, Folder 1144)
  - D(k)400 Salaried officers
    - D(k)410 General secretary and assistants
      - D(k)412 Qualifications
        - Directions Pour Les Etudes Des Candidats Secretaires (Box 156, Folder 1144)
  - D(k)500 Organized Lines of Work and Study. Religious Departments and Meetings. General Methods
    - General
      - Lauterburg. Principes D'Action, 1903 (Box 156, Folder 1144)
    - D(k)510 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
      - D(k)510.4 Meetings, announcements
        - Address, Aux etudiants des Universites suisses, on occasion of Mott's visit, 1911 (Box 156, Folder 1144)
      - D(k)512 Personal work texts
        - Items here are listed in card catalog (Box 157, Folder 1145)
        - Items here are listed in card catalog (Box 158, Folder 1146)
      - D(k)513 Life work in religious callings
        - Les Ministeres Chretiens, 1920 (Box 159, Folder 1147)
      - D(k)514 Work for schoolboys and schoolgirls
        - D(k)514.1 Camps
          - Leaflets/papers re. various camps, 1898-1916 (Box 159, Folder 1147)
      - D(k)518 The individual as citizen. The war. Church and state. Church history.
        - Favre. Experiences et Revelations, 1916 (Box 159, Folder 1148)
        - Neeser. La part de Dieu a la guerre, 1915 (Box 159, Folder 1148)
        - Micheli. Christianisme et democratie, 1914 (Box 159, Folder 1148)
        - de Morsier. La Question de la Paix, 1915 (Box 159, Folder 1148)
        - Reymond. Le Protestantisme et ses caracteres objectifs, 1918 (Box 159, Folder 1148)
        - Sabatier. Du Renouveau Catholique et des Dispositions que les Protestants Doivent avoir devant lui, 1908 (Box 159, Folder 1148)
      - D(k)519 Work for foreign students